# Ghazwa Alshammari

Certified Quality System Internal Audit QMS (ISO 9001: 2015)/SSYBP/SFC



## **Professional Summary**

IT Specialist with Quality Management System Auditor and or and Scrum Certification. Who's utilize my technical skills for achieving the best performance in the organization I would like to implement my innovative ideas, skills, and creativity for accomplishing the information technologies and quality management system to the fullest



2022- Now-

## **Work History**

Certified Quality System Internal Audi t - I T Specialist

### FNRCO CONSULTING COMPANY, Dammam, EP

- Awareness & Internal Audit I SO 9001: 2015
- Developing a Baseline Study
- Developing the Integrated Quality Management
   Manual System (ISO 9001, 14001, 45001)
- Developing Training Program
- Developing a Website
- Developing a Costing Sheet
- Developing Business Plan
- Development in the recruitment department
- Developing Human Resources and Talent Management Business Module



#### **Address**

Dhahran, 34258

#### **Phone**

054-783-7490

#### E-mail

Alshammari995@outlook.com



Management System
Development



Computer Technician



Information Technology Management



Baseline



**Quality Management** 



Marketing



2021-2022

## Computer Technician

- Specialized Drawing & Design Trading Est
- Developed shared excel sheet for orders to ensure
- That no orders list, forgotten, or delayed

2019-2022

### **Administrative Assist ant**

### **FAT foundation**

- Hiring Training and developing new employees
- Organizing employees files (system- manual)

Management system development



Microsoft Office



2018-2018

### **Administrative**

Kids Garden

- School Development
- Data entry

Awareness & Internal I SO 9001: 2015



### Languages



English



Arabic



2015-2015

### Marketing

- Bank Aljazira Takaful Aljazira
- Money saving



Eng. Fahad Ameer +966 507 000 047

Amal Sal eh +966 56 236 7701



## Education

2016-2017

**IT Diploma** 

University of Dammam

### **Bachelor of Information System**

2019- Now

Arab Open University



## **Accomplishments**

- Quality Management System I S O 9001: 2015 F M- QMS- 51892
- Si x Sigma Yellow Bel t 856209
- Awareness & internal I SO 9001: 2015
- Scrum Fundamentals Certified 929958
- Computer Technician
- Saudi Council of Engineers
- Intensive English
- English language skills -Arab Open University
- English language skills Al Bassam Institute
- Cybersecurity curser 2132
- Negotiation Associate: 590874
- Marketing Strategy Associate: 605758
- Corporate Sales Associate: 603722
- Digital Marketing Associate:607702
- Marketing Research Associate: 603553
- Course Human Resources Droob
- Project Management Foundations LinkedIn LEARNING
- Course Human Resources Foundation LinkedIn LEARNING